hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨， Spring 粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装Spring 提示
installment we're gonna look at a very
分期付款，我们将看一个非常
interesting pattern which I was recently
我最近的有趣模式
reminded of called hedging now hedging
想起了被称为对冲现在的对冲
is a pattern that makes it easy for
是一种易于操作的模式
clients that have a deadline or an SLA
有期限或SLA的客户
sort of driven sort of use case to
某种驱动的用例
achieve that use case by making multiple
通过制作多个来实现该用例
calls in concurrent and responding with
并发调用并响应
the first request that returns basically
基本返回的第一个请求
so if you make a call to a service and
因此，如果您致电服务，
that service is going to a garbage
该服务将成为垃圾
garbage collection pause or it's down or
垃圾收集暂停或已关闭或
it's got some latency or whatever you
会有一些延迟或其他
know whatever hiccup might be causing it
知道可能是什么打h
to be in trouble well you just you make
麻烦就解决了
multiple calls and you hedge your bet
多次通话，您对冲您的赌注
that one of them will return in time by
他们中的一个会及时返回
making multiple calls so that you have
拨打多个电话，以便您拥有
one that will succeed that you know
一个你会成功的人
whatever ones if the other ones come
如果其他人来的话
back great you know but if they don't
返回伟大，你知道，但如果他们不知道
that's fine too you can just discard
很好，你也可以丢弃
them right you don't need them this of
他们对，你不需要他们的
course only works if you can make calls
课程只有在您可以拨打电话的情况下才有效
multiple times you know they have to be
多次，你知道他们必须
impotent right they have to be they have
他们必须是无能的权利
to be able to survive multiple calls
能够承受多次通话
without any undue sort of observed side
没有任何不必要的观察到的一面
effects so it's a very interesting
效果，所以非常有趣
pattern now this is a one of those kinds
模式，这是其中一种
of patterns that requires a service
需要服务的模式
registry right there's a lot of things
注册表中有很多东西
that we could do and we talked about in
我们可以做的，我们在
a cognitive architecture we talked about
我们谈论的认知架构
service registries a lot because there's
服务注册中心很多，因为
a lot of patterns that go beyond what we
许多超越我们的模式
can do with just regular DNS right DNS
可以使用常规DNS进行正确的DNS
is a is useful but it is not for a lot
是有用的，但不是很多
of use cases sufficient so DNS tells me
用例足够，所以DNS告诉我
where something is supposed to live not
本应居住的地方
if it's alive right and that difference
如果它还活着，那区别
is important knowing if a service is
了解服务是否重要很重要
awake and alive and able to respond it's
醒着，还活着并且能够回应它
very different from knowing you know the
与知道您有很大不同
location of that service I need to be
该服务的位置我需要
able to in order to be able to do
为了能够做
different kinds of load bouncing client
不同种类的负载反弹客户端
side note balancing I was able to
边注平衡我能够
control that on the client I want to
控制我想要的客户端
build to have more control over the
建立更多的控制权
routing from a client to a service and I
从客户端路由到服务，我
can control that on the client as well
也可以在客户端上控制
so that's another use case where having
所以这是另一个用例
the ability to talk to a service
与服务对话的能力
registry and then ask the service
注册表，然后询问服务
registry for any of a number of
注册表中的任何一个
different services that are out there
不同的服务在那里
and then being able to make the decision
然后能够做出决定
based on any kind of criteria or
基于任何类型的标准或
predicates whatever that can be that can
谓词可以是什么
be very
很
especially if you have very particular
特别是如果你非常特别
load-balancing kinds of use cases for
负载均衡的各种用例
example suppose you want to do
这个例子假设你想做
multi-tenancy or data center awareness
多租户或数据中心意识
or these kinds of things sharding
或这些东西分片
whatever it is you can do this if you
不管是什么，如果您可以这样做
understand how many instances of a given
了解给定的实例数
service you have and their locations
您所拥有的服务及其位置
also DNS has some limitations and you
DNS也有一些限制，您
can easily fairly easily get around them
可以很容易地绕过他们
but it is just one of those things and
但这只是其中之一
you have to remember to do for example
你要记得做例如
DNS clients like Java will cache
像Java这样的DNS客户端将缓存
resolved IP addresses so if you go to
解析的IP地址，所以如果您转到
DNS server the DNS server gives you an
DNS服务器DNS服务器为您提供了
IP address the Java client will keep
Java客户端将保留的IP地址
that and then route subsequent requests
然后路由后续请求
not to the DNS server but to the IP
而不是DNS服务器，而是IP
address and so that all that means that
地址，所以这意味着
the clients will end up unfairly
客户最终会受到不公平的对待
dogpiling on the the first IP address
跟踪第一个IP地址
that's been resolved in NJ Miam next
接下来在NJ Miam中解决了
time you restart the JVM it might
当您重新启动JVM时，它可能
resolve obviously you can fix this by
解决显然可以解决此问题
setting your DNS to have a time to live
设置您的DNS有时间
value of 0 and then you you know climb
值为0，然后您知道爬升
them do the right thing but you know
他们做正确的事，但你知道
these are the kinds of thing you have to
这些是您必须要做的事情
remember and they're not exactly front
记住，他们并不完全在前面
and center they're buried I think what
和中心，他们被埋葬，我想
most of us would consider sort of arcane
我们大多数人会考虑某种神秘的东西
configuration parameters so we don't
配置参数，所以我们不
what I have to do on these kinds of
我在这些类型上要做的
things and so this pattern hedging is
事情，所以这种模式对冲是
just one of those things where it just
这些只是其中之一
really works well with a service
真的可以很好地服务
registry because you need the ability to
注册表，因为您需要具备以下能力
ask something for two or three or n you
问两三个或三个你
know distinct instances of a given
知道给定的不同实例
service so what we're gonna do is we're
服务，所以我们要做的就是
gonna use a service registry and it can
将使用服务注册表，它可以
be used in it you can use any service
在其中使用您可以使用任何服务
registry that spring cloud supports
Spring Cloud支持的注册表
rites of spring clubs got the discovery
Spring 俱乐部的仪式得到了发现
client abstraction and the discovery
客户端抽象和发现
kind abstraction gives you the ability
善良的抽象为您提供了能力
to ask the question what instances are
问一个问题是什么实例
there given a service ID and there's an
给了一个服务ID，还有一个
implementation for this interface
此接口的实现
supporting Cloud Foundry for supporting
支持Cloud Foundry支持
kubernetes supporting Netflix is a
支持Netflix的kubernetes是
Eureka Apache zookeeper has she called
尤里卡·阿帕奇 Zookeeper 叫她
console I mean you know probably more
控制台，我的意思是你可能知道更多
I'm forgetting so well we're gonna go
我忘了我们要走了
ahead and build a new service a new
前进并建立新的服务
service registry using the spring
使用Spring的服务注册表
initializer here called Eureka
这里的初始化程序称为Eureka
I'm just gonna make it a ravika server
我只是要使其成为ravika服务器
like so and we'll hit generate and we'll
像这样，我们将点击生成，我们将
open that up in our IDE there we are
在我们的IDE中打开它
and so we're gonna say open this up I'm
所以我们要说打开这个
using my little command line script here
在这里使用我的小命令行脚本
of course as always too
当然也一如既往
to open up the project but I'm you know
打开项目，但我知道
you can you could use a wizard and tide
你可以用向导和潮汐
of intelligent you like excuse me little
就像你一样聪明
second all right
第二好
so I'm going to open this up already the
所以我要打开它了
application of properties thank you and
属性的应用谢谢和
you want the Rika server application
您想要Rika服务器应用程序
itself good and evil you mica server
云母服务器本身的好与坏
very good and our job is just to
非常好，我们的工作只是
configure this so it's a listing in the
进行配置，以便在
standard place where we can expect to
我们可以期待的标准地方
find at a 761 what it's held to not
在761找到不持有的东西
register itself and not to fetch the
注册自己，而不是获取
data from himself basically so that's it
基本上就是他自己的数据
once I do that that wouldn't normally be
一旦我这样做，通常不会
enough but we're running in Java 11 and
足够，但是我们在Java 11和
actually I'm not even sure if this will
实际上我什至不确定这是否会
work we'll try it but we need Java 11
工作，我们将尝试它，但我们需要Java 11
where we're going to have 11 I'm using
我要用的地方是11
Java 11 this works just fine I'm Davin 8
Java 11正常工作，我是Davin 8
of course and and probably 9 and 10 but
当然，大概是9和10但
in John 11 they moved out some API is
在约翰福音11章中，他们搬出了一些API
that were part of Java EE those are no
是Java EE的一部分，不是
longer bundled in the core JDK which is
不再捆绑在核心JDK中
overall a great thing TM right it allows
总的来说，这是一件很棒的事情
the JDK team to move faster and so on
JDK团队加快行动速度等等
but in the meantime that means that we
但与此同时，这意味着我们
have to wear appropriate bundles jars
必须穿合适的捆绑罐
manually and that's not a big deal
手动，那没什么大不了的
that's the nature of dependency
这就是依赖的本质
management for now that's not being
暂时的管理
taken care of for us by supreme cloud
至尊云照顾我们
but I suspect that would be fixed in no
但我怀疑这肯定会解决
time so for now all I've done is I've
时间，所以现在我要做的就是
added the Jax be API is here Jack speak
添加了Jax be API，在这里杰克讲
or Jax be implicit evasion stuff and
或Jax是隐式回避的东西，
again this is all very nicely extract
再次，这都是很好的提取
out into a property like so Dex be that
进入像这样的属性
version alright to replace all very good
版本可以替换所有非常好的
so there you go so now it's just I can
所以你去那里，现在就是我可以
change in one place all right now let's
一处改变现在让我们
go ahead and kick this off
继续并开始
all righty so there it is if it's up and
好吧，如果有，那就在那里
running it's available for use and we
运行它可以使用，我们
can confirm as much by visiting the the
可以通过访问
service on its configured host in port
端口上已配置主机上的服务
which of course in this case is
在这种情况下，哪个当然是
localhost 87-61 so there we are no
localhost 87-61，所以我们没有
instances yet nothing nothing registered
实例还没有什么都没有注册
so now let's go ahead and build a simple
所以现在让我们继续构建一个简单的
service we're gonna just build a brand
服务，我们将建立一个品牌
new service this service is going to
该服务将要提供的新服务
have the smarts that it needs to be able
拥有需要的智慧
to register with him with the the
向他注册
registry so I'm gonna call this you know
注册表，所以我叫这个你知道
imagine it really enough service and we
想象它真的足够的服务，我们
use the eureka support do you you week a
使用尤里卡支持，你一周吗
client support weenies Lombok and the
客户支持weenies龙目岛和
reactive web support okay so we're gonna
响应式网络支持，好的，我们要
build an application this is the other
建立一个应用程序，这是另一个
thing that's nice about this pattern is
这种模式的优点是
it lends itself to reactive programming
它适合于反应式编程
actually so this is a great example when
实际上，这是一个很好的例子
these two things really complement each
这两件事真的相互补充
other they they they they multiply each
其他他们他们他们他们相乘
other okay so we're gonna go ahead and
好的，所以我们要继续
hit generate and that'll give us a
点击生成，这会给我们一个
another project here downloads you a
这里的另一个项目会下载您一个
service dip and our service I think is
服务下降，我们认为我们的服务是
gonna be straightforward we don't you
直截了当，我们不是你
know we're not actually trying to test
知道我们实际上不是在尝试测试
that we can write a service what we're
我们可以写一个服务
trying to test is that we can you know
尝试测试的是，我们可以知道吗
make multiple heads to calls to that
多次呼吁
service and so the service itself is
服务，因此服务本身就是
pretty immaterial right it doesn't have
它没有
to be doesn't have to be particularly
不必特别
interesting all we want to do is have
有趣的是，我们要做的是
something able to create an artificial
能够创造人造物的东西
delay that will will then be able to
延迟将能够
sort of randomly prolong the lifetime of
随机延长寿命
a request and so we can see that one
一个请求，所以我们可以看到一个
returns before the other so let's do
返回之前，让我们做
that here let's go to our service
我们在这里为我们服务
application and what's the easiest thing
应用程序，最简单的事情是什么
we can do I guess we want just an
我们可以做到，我想我们只想要一个
endpoint reactive endpoint or not you
端点反应性端点或不是
know just we just need any endpoint
知道我们只需要任何端点
suppose this part doesn't have to be
假设这部分不必是
reactive at all
完全没有反应
so get mapping hi
所以得到映射嗨
string wheat and what we want to do we
串小麦和我们想做什么
want to have a a rest controller right
想拥有一个正确的 rest controller
it's a rest controller and we want this
这是一个 rest controller ，我们想要这个
thing to be a an object that will have a
成为一个将具有
delay and our delay will be the we want
延迟，我们的延迟将是我们想要的
to have a little bit of randomness here
在这里有一点随机性
so what we're gonna do is we're gonna
所以我们要做的是
say give me the longest of two random
说给我最长的两个随机
numbers okay and I guess we can wouldn't
数字还可以，我想我们不会
want here let's see void random we'll
想要在这里让我们看看虚无随机
have random random next long okay and
下一个很长一段时间随机
I'm gonna multiply this times some
我要乘这个倍
number of seconds so times a thousand
秒数乘以一千
seconds okay times seconds and we're
几秒钟还可以，我们
gonna return alone so there we are said
要一个人回来所以我们说
okay that looks that looks fairly
好吧，看起来还不错
straightforward to me okay so I'm gonna
对我来说很简单，所以我要
say give me the longest of two numbers
说给我两个数字中最长的一个
of two random durations so whatever
两个随机的持续时间
whichever these two delays takes the
这两个延迟中的任何一个都会导致
longest I'm gonna use that one and then
最长我要用那个然后
I'm just gonna artificially sleep which
我要人为地睡觉
is the least elegant thing ever but you
是最不优雅的东西，但你
know it does the job here and that of
知道它在这里和
course requires an exception so well
当然需要一个例外
that's a method signature and then
这是方法签名，然后
finally having done all that hard work
终于做了所有的努力
I'm gonna say screen message equals
我要说屏幕信息等于
hello whoa that jello look jello but not
你好，那个果冻看起来果冻，但不是
that jello hello
那你好你好
you know after play
你知道比赛后
ms okay then we're just gonna churn that
女士好，那么我们只是搅动一下
message so that way we'll have ability
信息，这样我们将有能力
to see what's been how long the service
看看服务多久了
you know waiting for us okay or how long
你知道等我们好还是多久
we had to wait for that service call
我们不得不等待那个服务电话
okay so there we go we've got now a
好吧，现在我们去了
service is that enough I think we need
服务足够我想我们需要
to we need to so I want to run this
到我们需要的位置，所以我要运行此
application multiple times and so as
多次申请等等
results I'm gonna make it distinct I'm
结果我要让它与众不同
gonna give it some distinct
给它一些独特的
configuration so that I can run the
配置，以便我可以运行
application multiple times and not have
多次申请并且没有
it stomp on each you know not have each
它足了你所不知道的每一个
instance stomp on each other on the same
实例彼此踩踏
host again this isn't such a big deal in
再次主持这不是什么大不了的
different hosts but it becomes more
不同的主机，但它变得更多
interesting in a demo scenario like this
在这样的演示场景中很有趣
so first I'm gonna say I want you to run
所以首先我要说我要你跑步
on a different port 0 and then the
在另一个端口0上，然后
second I'm gonna give it a name frana
第二，我要给它起一个名字frança
application name equals service this is
应用程序名称等于服务，这是
the name by which it will register in
它将在其中注册的名称
the registry I'm gonna give him the ID
注册表我要给他身份证
and the ID I'll just derive service I
和我将要派生的ID
want this to be resolved once so I'll
希望这个问题能够解决一次，所以我会
just extract that in table here I'm
只需将其提取到表中
going to use a pseudo property you know
将使用您知道的伪属性
a very interesting property inside of a
一个内部非常有趣的属性
spring called random dot int and here
Spring 叫做随机点整数，这里
I'm gonna provide a range so one out of
我要提供一个范围
999 and then I'm going to use that to
999，然后我将使用它来
create you Iike instanceid okay there we
在这里创建您Iike instanceid好的
are so that's the this will give me a
是的，这将给我一个
random name each each instance each
每个实例每个随机命名
client that registered in the registry
在注册表中注册的客户端
will have a different label basically
基本上会有不同的标签
it's assigned to it and we're gonna
它被分配给它，我们要
establish that label once so it's
一次建立那个标签
consistent across the lifetime of this
在整个生命周期中保持一致
of this service okay we don't have to do
这项服务好了，我们不必做
anything else because right by default
其他任何事情，因为默认情况下正确
you Miko's running on the default port
您的Miko在默认端口上运行
and it's gonna use the spring Cloud
它会使用 Spring 的云
discovery client abstraction
发现客户端抽象
implementation to talk to that so yeah
实现与之交谈，是的
let's just go ahead and oh we have to do
让我们继续前进，哦，我们必须做
one more thing in the telogen we have to
telogen中还有另一件事
turn off the single instance only hit
关闭仅单个实例
apply and go so let's see hit okay
申请并继续前进，让我们看看成功吧
one okay take two okay and good measure
一个可以，两个可以，并且很好
it's just doing a third time and if we
这只是第三次，如果我们
go to our registry we see we have three
去我们的注册表，我们看到我们有三个
instances of the service right here
这里的服务实例
right that's where it says three
正确的是它说三个
instances and they're called service
实例，它们被称为服务
seven one one five service three nine
七一一五服务三九
three eight nine six and service seven
三八九六和服务七
one four eight okay so now they're
一四八好吧，现在他们是
accessible they're visible if I you if I
如果我可以访问，它们是可见的
to point to some other service to this
指向其他服务
node to the service registry I could
我可以连接到服务注册表的节点
programmatically ask for how many
以编程方式询问多少
instances there are out there of the
实例在那里
service I don't get back three service
服务我不回三服务
instances and that's what we're gonna do
实例，这就是我们要做的
with another client now to talk to our
现在与另一位客户与我们交谈
service via the searchers you can
通过搜索者提供服务
resolve instances through the service
通过服务解析实例
registry now this is a this is also
注册表现在这是这也是
going to use as before our service
将像以前一样使用
registry support so eureka discovery
注册表支持，因此尤里卡发现
would use Lombok we use the reactive web
将使用龙目岛，我们使用反应堆
support actuator just because that's
支持执行器只是因为
good clean cloud hygiene right and I
好的清洁云卫生对，我
think that's pretty much it I can't
认为那是我做不到的
imagine what else we would need got the
想象我们还需要什么
reactive web got Eureka got the actuator
反应网得到尤里卡得到了执行器
we've got the lumbar support and reactor
我们有腰部支撑和反应器
gets brought in automatically so I'll
被自动带入，所以我会
hit client it jimmied and you a oh my
打客户它吉米，你一个哦，我的
okay now same thing as before we need
好吧，现在和我们需要的一样
this application to start up and it's
该应用程序启动，它是
gonna suppose we should pick a different
假设我们应该选择其他
port just in case okay
港口以防万一
and our application is going to be a
我们的应用程序将是
REST API in itself that will make a
REST API本身将使
reactive web client call to another node
反应性Web客户端调用到另一个节点
and so we'll say this is gonna be a
所以我们会说这将是一个
class 10 dig lesson2 folder all right
第10类dig lesson2文件夹
and we'll say at rest controller and our
我们会说 rest controller 和我们的
that's its think about this we want to
这就是我们想要的想法
get the message right so we'll have a in
得到正确的信息，所以我们将在
point here that returns a string greet
点这里返回一个字符串问候
and in order to make this call you know
为了打电话，你知道
some well case although what the the
一些很好的情况，虽然
client will make a call to hedge you
客户会打电话给您套期保值
know like that and then in order to make
知道那样，然后使
that call we need a reactive web client
那个电话我们需要一个反应式的网络客户端
this is a HTTP client that's interesting
这是一个有趣的HTTP客户端
framework 5 or later and it's a it's
框架5或更高版本，它是
reactive so it doesn't block the client
反应性的，因此不会阻止客户端
client thread if at all possible and so
客户端线程（如果可能的话）
we need to instantiate we need to
我们需要实例化，我们需要
factory an instance of that so we create
工厂的一个实例，所以我们创建
a web client
网络客户端
bean here turn web client builder that
bean 在这里打开Web客户端生成器
build all right now this isn't in of
现在建立所有这不在
itself enough we need to actually
本身就足够了，我们实际上需要
configure a filter that does the work of
配置一个可以完成工作的过滤器
doing the hedging so let's see what the
做对冲，让我们看看
naive version without the hedging looks
天真的版本，没有套期保值的外观
like docket dot URI forward slash
像小圆点URI正斜杠
service /pi okay and then we're going to
服务/ pi好的，然后我们将
say we retrieve the data that comes back
说我们检索返回的数据
and just turn it into a payload of type
并把它变成类型的有效载荷
class string in that class rather so
该类中的类字符串相当
that would actually give us assuming
这实际上会让我们假设
this was a valid hostname this would
这是一个有效的主机名
work and some of you may know that you
工作，有些人可能知道你
can even do if there's even a
甚至可以做到
load-balanced annotation in spring cloud
Spring Cloud中的负载平衡注释
and the way that works is you say web
而有效的方式就是您说网络
client dot builder builder and in this
客户点生成器生成器，在此
case you don't actually build the
如果你实际上没有建立
building yourself you
建立你自己
the website yourself you use the Builder
您自己使用Builder的网站
and then you continue customizing it but
然后您继续自定义它，但是
basically spring cloud will Auto
基本上Spring Cloud会自动
configure a builder instance that you
配置您要构建的构建器实例
know it's ready for you to build as I'm
知道我已经准备好为您构建
doing it here or to further customize
在这里做或进一步定制
but in this case because I have at
但在这种情况下，因为我在
load-balanced I've told spring cloud to
负载均衡我已经告诉Spring Cloud
create a web builder a web client
创建Web构建器Web客户端
builder for me and to configure a load
我的构建器并配置负载
balancing filter an exchange filter
平衡过滤器交换过滤器
function that and that handles that pre
并处理该预
processes every HTTP request that I make
处理我发出的每个HTTP请求
and it's going to in this case extract
在这种情况下，它将被提取
out the hostname it's gonna identify
找出主机名
that it's going to treat that as a
它会将其视为
service ID in the service registry and
服务注册表中的服务ID和
it's gonna talk to the service registry
要和服务注册中心谈谈
using the discovery client abstraction
使用发现客户端抽象
so that is kind of what we want but we
所以这就是我们想要的，但是我们
want that that hedging behavior so this
想要那种避险行为，所以这
isn't exactly what what we want the same
到底是不是我们想要的一样
thing so you know keep keep that in mind
事情，所以你知道记住这一点
and what I'm gonna show you today you
还有我今天要告诉你的
could extract out into such a filter we
可以提取到这样的过滤器中
can you know create audio figuration
你能知道创建音频配置吗
that you know add a hedge or something
你知道加树篱之类的东西
like that I don't but that's certainly
像那样，我不是，但是那肯定是
an exercise for maybe the next video who
下一个视频的练习者
knows you know but in the meantime we'll
知道你知道，但与此同时我们会
build it ourselves so we have the
自己建造它，所以我们有
ability to customize at all okay so
完全可以自定义的能力
there's this and now we do we do need a
就是这个，现在我们要做的是
filter totally so I said that the the
完全过滤，所以我说了
meat of this work will be done in a
这项工作的实质将在
filter but I'm gonna call the hedge
过滤器，但我要称呼树篱
exchange filter function this is going
交换过滤器功能这是要去的
to implement the exchange filter
实现交换过滤器
function the contract in spring class a
履行 Spring A类合同
spring in the spring term of five okay
Spring 五学期还好
and you know jobs fairly straightforward
而且您知道工作相当简单
we want to UM implement the filter
我们想要UM实施过滤器
method here filter is the only one
方法这里过滤器是唯一的
that's that's required the rest are
那是必需的，其余的是
actually default functions so you can
实际上是默认功能，因此您可以
see it says default and then default
看到它说默认，然后默认
apply etc we can do that because this
应用等我们可以做到，因为这
API assumes spring frame of five and
API假定Spring 框架为5，
assumes Java 8 and it assumes default
假定Java 8并且假定默认
methods okay so we've got now a filter
方法还可以，所以我们现在有一个过滤器
that is going to be given a chance to
这将有机会
process the request process it and then
处理请求，然后处理
forward it on to the next filter
转发给下一个过滤器
Chane if this looks anything like the
如果这看起来像
servlet filter API good now you can you
servlet过滤器API很好，现在可以了
should have a pretty good idea of what's
应该对什么有一个很好的主意
happening here we're actually have a you
发生在这里，我们实际上有一个你
have a chain of different filters that
有一系列不同的过滤器
are gonna be put into play here we we
将在这里发挥作用，我们
want to use them to process this request
想要使用它们来处理此请求
I'm gonna do a lot of the same work that
我要做很多相同的工作
the load bouncer exchanged filter
负载弹跳器更换过滤器
function does the one with the Hat load
函数用Hat加载一个
balance so we're gonna do a lot of that
平衡，所以我们要做很多
same work because we do after all need
相同的工作，因为我们毕竟需要
to resolve this via DNS I'm sorry via
通过DNS解决这个问题，我很抱歉
the service registry but we need to do
服务注册表，但我们需要做
so and then given those choices we need
因此，鉴于这些选择，我们需要
to pick the one that comes back first so
挑选一个最先回来的
it's a different goal isn't it it's a
这是一个不同的目标，不是吗？
little bit further so our our exchange
一点点，所以我们我们的交流
filter function is going to depend on a
过滤器功能将取决于
discovery client spring cloud discovery
发现客户端Spring Cloud发现
client will depend upon a else do we
客户将取决于其他我们
need I guess we need a load balancer
需要我猜我们需要一个负载均衡器
client this is the load balancer client
客户端，这是负载均衡器客户端
and spring clouds is what's used to
Spring 的云是用来
alter the latest defaults to ribon ribon
将最新的默认值更改为ribon ribon
is a client-side load balancer also
也是客户端负载均衡器
about my Netflix but this load
关于我的Netflix但这个负载
downstroke line adapts it so that
下行程线使其适应
doesn't doesn't only work with Netflix
不只与Netflix合作
types and Netflix projects like Netflix
类型和Netflix项目（例如Netflix）
Eureka and I suppose we went to some
尤里卡和我想我们去了一些
definition of you know how many attempts
你的定义知道多少次尝试
we want to make and then the max
我们要制造然后最大
attempts right so let's say we want to
尝试正确，所以我们想
make three calls but you know doesn't
打了三个电话，但你不知道
work so you want to escape when I keep
工作，所以当我继续时你想逃跑
trying until until max okay okay so
尝试直到最大okay okay这样
there we go so those are three variables
我们去那里，所以这是三个变量
are the are sorry are four parameters
是对不起是四个参数
okay those is constructor arguments here
好的，这些是构造函数参数
and of course you can imagine these
当然你可以想象这些
would be configuration values or
将是配置值或
something like that driven by
像是由
configuration properties for our
我们的配置属性
purposes we're gonna say that we want
目的是我们要说我们想要
the max attempts to be attempts times
最大尝试次数为尝试次数
two okay
两个还好
and the attempts themselves you know as
和你自己的尝试
I suppose I suppose this doesn't even
我想我想这甚至都没有
need to be defined here we can just make
需要在这里定义，我们可以使
this simpler for now you can privatize
现在更简单，您可以私有化
things to your heart's content later but
事情事后让您满意
let's just keep a little simple
让我们保持简单
okay so we're gonna use a load balancer
好吧，我们要使用负载平衡器
client when we use the discovery client
使用发现客户端时的客户端
we can use the attempts and then and
我们可以使用尝试然后
then we do need to have some default
那么我们确实需要一些默认值
configuration so I think and I want to
配置，所以我想，我想
have a separate constructor since I'm
我有一个单独的构造函数
just using component scanning I need
只需要使用组件扫描
tell spring cloud how to resolve this
告诉Spring Cloud如何解决这个问题
this dependency and I think for this one
这种依赖，我想为此
I'll just use a load balancer client and
我将只使用一个负载平衡器客户端，
I discovered client that would be C T C
我发现将是CTC的客户
we'll just assume that you gave us a
我们只是假设您给了我们一个
default value of their of let's say 3
假设其默认值为3
because that's what we got running on a
因为这就是我们在
machine right now isn't it okay so that
机器现在不行，所以
means okay good so we've got that now
表示很好，所以我们现在就知道了
and now for the work the actual hard
现在，对于实际工作来说，
work in it and I use that it with air
在其中工作，我将其与空气一起使用
quotes here because it's not such a big
在这里引用，因为它没有那么大
deal what we're gonna do is we're gonna
处理我们要做的是
say when the request comes in want to
说当请求进入想要
get the original URI write original URI
获取原始URI写原始URI
of the requests coming in java.net and
来自java.net的请求中
the request is of course on the URL
该请求当然在URL上
itself and then from there we want to
本身，然后从那里我们想要
get the string service ID I think and
获取我认为的字符串服务ID
that's going to be the original URI get
这将是原始URI获取
host and then from there we want to get
主机，然后从那里我们想要得到
a collection a list of service instances
集合的服务实例列表
services that match this service ID and
与此服务ID相匹配的服务，以及
we do that using the discovery client we
我们使用发现客户端来做到这一点
get instances for the service ID okay
获取服务ID的实例好
that's okay I forgot enough space there
没关系，我在那里忘记了足够的空间
good and then from there what to count
好，然后从那里算什么
so we're gonna say why don't we want to
所以我们要说为什么我们不想
launch a number of different calls at
在发起多个不同的通话
the same time okay so we're gonna need
好的，所以我们需要
to store each of those launched ships
存放每艘发射船
basically each way you know when it's
基本上每种方式你知道什么时候
launched a bunch of ships into the night
发射了一堆船到深夜
basically and each ship will go out and
基本上，每艘船都会出去
make a request and then come back to us
提出要求，然后再回来找我们
and whatever comes back first will keep
一切先回来都会保持
so new hash map
所以新的哈希图
and you know what I just realized
你知道我刚刚意识到的
since we're gonna we're gonna run this
因为我们要运行这个
and we're gonna launch I'm gonna make
我们要推出我要
requests we're only gonna get the first
要求我们只会得到第一个
one that came back so we're not gonna
一个回来了，所以我们不会
see how long the other ones took so we
看看其他人花了多长时间，所以我们
need to actually announce that here in
需要在这里实际宣布
the service that I built a second ago so
我第二次建立的服务
let's go back to that service and make
让我们回到该服务并进行
sure we launch or we log out you know
确保我们启动或注销您知道的
this message okay good bye
这个消息好再见
goodbye
再见
okay and we use Lombok here
好吧，我们在这里使用龙目岛
message
信息
turning already so there's our message
已经在转弯，所以有我们的信息
okay so that way we'll see it in the
好的，这样我们就可以在
console so we'll see what could have
控制台，所以我们会看到可能
been the path not taken so to speak we
可以说我们没有走这条路
don't need to run these right now let's
现在不需要运行这些，让我们
just go back to our code and we'll read
只需回到我们的代码，我们将阅读
them in a second
他们在一秒钟内
okay so now we have a map that stores
好吧，现在我们有一张地图可以存储
all the different launched in flight
所有不同的在飞行中发射
requests and we're gonna say while the
请求，我们要说的是
size of the map is less than this start
地图的尺寸​​小于此起点
attempts and the counter is less than
尝试和计数器小于
this max attempts then we want to load
这个最大尝试，然后我们要加载
balance by using the load balancer
使用负载均衡器进行均衡
client and I'm going to choose from
客户，我要选择
among the service IDs and that will give
在服务ID中，这将给
us back a service instance and then from
我们返回一个服务实例，然后从
there we want to get the URI of that
在那里我们想要获取的URI
instance lb dot URI to ASCII string and
实例lb点URI到ASCII字符串和
then from there we want to make sure
然后从那里我们要确保
that we haven't already seen this one
那我们还没看过
before so if not ships dock contains key
在此之前，如果不发货，码头包含钥匙
ASCII string if it's not already there
ASCII字符串（如果尚未存在）
then we're gonna say ships dot and I
那我们要说的是舰船，而我
actually I suppose we could've just done
实际上我想我们可以完成
that instead huh but that would require
而是吧，但这需要
that we actually compute the result
我们实际计算结果
which I don't wanna do so we know we're
我不想这么做，所以我们知道
going to avoid I guess we could have
要避免我想我们可以
done this actually now would have an
做到这一点实际上现在将有一个
easier - yeah let's try that so let's
更容易-是的，让我们尝试一下，让我们
let's do that instead so instead I'm
让我们这样做，所以我
going to say compute if absent and it's
要说计算，如果不存在，那是
gonna be ASCII string and we're gonna
将是ASCII字符串，我们将
say if that string doesn't exist then
说如果该字符串不存在，那么
use give us the key and we use the key
用给我们钥匙，我们用钥匙
to to arrive at the value that has to be
以获得必须的价值
stored there which in this case is going
存储在这种情况下要去的地方
to be a motto of Claire response and so
成为克莱尔回应的座右铭，因此
that is where we're gonna actually have
那就是我们真正要去的地方
a call to actually make this request
实际发出此请求的电话
let's factor that out let's extract that
让我们将其提取出来
into a method here motto of client
客户的座右铭
response
响应
in bulk and we'll come back to this in a
大量，我们将在
second and what is that going to do I
第二，那我该怎么办
guess that's gonna say in bulk
猜猜这会说很多
okay that looks fairly straightforward
好吧，看起来很简单
doesn't it
不是吗
so that bad okay we need to actually
所以不好，我们实际上需要
parameterize that don't we so okay so
参数化我们不那么好吧
while that's happening you know what
在发生这种情况时，您知道
will happen when this is done we'll have
完成后将会发生
a bunch of maps with client responses in
一堆带有客户响应的地图
them right and we'll have a map on a
他们正确，我们将在地图上
bunch of client response my nose and
一堆客户反应我的鼻子和
publishers now these are reactive these
现在，发布商对这些有反应
types have not executed yet right that's
类型尚未执行，正确的是
the whole point of this is that it
整个要点是
hasn't executed yet and the reason
还没有执行，原因
that's interesting is because they only
有趣的是，因为他们只
get executed once there once they're
一旦他们在那里就被执行
subscribed to their endurance they're
订阅了他们的耐力
like the Java 8 streams in Canada you
就像加拿大的Java 8流一样
have to activate them you have to
必须激活它们，你必须
execute that we have to to to subscribe
执行我们必须订阅
to them to drain them okay I'm not sure
给他们排干好吧，我不确定
I need to see it maybe we'll leave it
我需要看到它，也许我们会离开它
there
那里
and then it so you know basically we can
然后就知道了，基本上我们可以
create as many of these as you want but
创建任意数量的这些，但是
all we're defining is a pipeline not the
我们定义的只是管道而不是
actual request over the wire and we can
通过电线的实际要求，我们可以
when we do make the request because the
当我们提出要求时，因为
reactive the scheduler can schedule
反应性的调度程序可以调度
these things concurrently which is very
这些东西并发，这是非常
convenient okay so now for the request
方便，好的，现在就提出要求
itself for the invocation of the request
本身用于调用请求
we need to we need to have the service
我们需要我们需要服务
instance I would think that seems useful
实例，我认为这似乎很有用
so where's our instance it's LV and we
所以我们的实例是LV，我们
want to have the original URI and we
想拥有原始URI，我们
want to have the request and we want to
想要请求，我们想要
have the next one in the chain
在链中有下一个
okay so let's change the signature to
好吧，让我们将签名更改为
accommodate this service instance okay
容纳这个服务实例好
client requests all right now we're
客户现在就要求我们
going to invoke that and that will in
将要调用它，这将在
turn
转
that will in turn require us to actually
进而需要我们实际
make the call so how do we do that let's
打电话，我们该怎么做，让我们
think about this we've got the service
考虑一下，我们已经提供了服务
instance we've got the URI so we just
实例，我们有URI，所以我们只是
need to actually make the request right
需要实际做出正确的请求
this is in this code is more or less
这在这段代码中或多或少
exactly what you would've found in the
确切地说，您会在
load balancing exchange filter function
负载均衡交换过滤功能
as well so you know we're gonna do that
以及，所以你知道我们要去做
so once a URI you're right equals this
所以一旦URI正确就等于
dot load balance your client got
客户获得的点负载平衡
reconstruct your I so what this is gonna
重建你的我，那会是什么
do is it's going to given a service
要做的是提供服务
instance that we have chosen and given
我们选择并给出的实例
the original URI you know the original
您知道原始的原始URI
you I said you know HTTP calling for
你我说你知道HTTP要求
such for such service it's going to
这样的服务将
replace that with the IP that's in the
将其替换为
service instance if service instance has
服务实例（如果服务实例具有）
things like host and port and scheme and
主机和端口以及方案等
your I and so it's good so it's just
你我，所以很好，就是
gonna process that URL for us very
要为我们非常处理该网址
nicely it's gonna build up a new URI
很好，它将建立一个新的URI
which is easy easy to do using Java net
使用Java net容易做到
URI because it's very easy to build a
URI，因为构建一个
prize that way yeah so client request we
以这种方式奖励是的，所以客户要求我们
this is gonna be the new request isn't
这将是新的要求不是
it so this will be the new request and
所以这将是新的要求，
I'll say client request dot create
我会说客户请求点创建
request dot method and what else do we
请求点方法以及我们还有什么
want
想
oh we need the URL already and we'll say
哦，我们已经需要网址了，我们会说
headers and we're gonna say once Ilona
标头，我们要说一次伊洛娜
all we're trying to do is to copy all
我们要做的就是复制所有
the stuff from the old one into the new
从旧的东西到新的东西
one right so header is done and all
一种权利，所以头已完成，所有
headers right but I guess we'll do the
标头正确，但我想我们会做
same thing here for the cookies C dot at
饼干的C点在这里也是一样
all right yeah that's right outside to
是的，对，就是
request
请求
request Dutch cookies and request on
要求荷兰饼干，并要求
headers okay call H make it a little
标头还可以，请致电H
easier to parse okay so the headers are
更容易解析，所以标头是
for each header H and each set cookie
对于每个标题H和每个设置的cookie
see you know if they can fix that when
看到你知道他们是否可以解决这个问题
add the thing from the requests itself
从请求本身添加东西
and then we'll have the attributes
然后我们将拥有属性
request to attributes right so I have to
请求正确的属性，所以我必须
view it to Metro I keep auto auto
查看它到地铁我保持自动
competing on the ones that are the
竞争那些
singular form of those things so a a I
这些东西的单数形式所以我
put all and this is going to be the
放所有，这将是
request dot attributes and what else do
请求点属性以及其他功能
we need I'm not sure I guess that's it
我们需要不确定我是否就是这样
body will be request dot body okay and
身体会要求点身体好，并且
it looks like it's a fairly good clone
看起来它是一个相当不错的克隆
of the request hopefully I didn't miss
希望我没有错过
anything important but you know we'll
重要的事情，但是你知道我们会的
see I have a feeling so next now we
看到我的感觉，所以接下来我们
finally having done that let's invoke
终于完成了，让我们调用
the next you know downstream thing in
接下来你知道下游的东西
the chain exchange new request so the
链交换新请求，因此
downstream part of the filter will see
过滤器的下游部分将看到
the new body the new request you know
新的机构，您知道的新要求
this is a very common pattern even in
即使在
the filter even the Java servlet filter
过滤器，甚至Java servlet过滤器
API thing but of course this is the
API的东西，但这当然是
client side not the server side so it
客户端而不是服务器端，所以
works the same way but it is by no means
以相同的方式工作，但绝不是
the same it is asynchronous I'm
同样是异步的我
non-blocking and reactive
无阻塞和反应性
there is no server that API involved
没有涉及该API的服务器
here at all and of course it's on the
在这里，当然是在
client of the server so I'm going to do
服务器的客户端，所以我要去做
is finally I'm gonna say that I'm gonna
终于我要说我要
announce every single launched ship I'm
宣布我所拥有的每艘发射船
gonna do so by logging it out just so we
要通过注销来做到这一点，所以我们
have some sort of ability to look at
有某种能力看
what's happening to the plate and on the
盘子和盘子上发生了什么
server I say this dot log like it's just
服务器，我说这个点日志就像
log then we say launching new request
登录，然后我们说启动新请求
URI
URI
alright ok that looks ok that looks
好吧，看起来不错，看起来
fairly straightforward I guess so here
我想这很简单
finally is where the middle rubber meets
终于是中间橡胶相遇的地方
the road right so when you say flux dot
正确的道路，所以当您说通量点
first very convenient give it a
首先很方便给它一个
publisher of things subscribe to all of
事物发布者订阅所有内容
them in the first one that's you know
他们在第一个是你知道的
completes we determine right so there's
完成我们确定正确的，所以有
our that's the magic of the algorithm if
如果这是算法的魔力，
you well that's all that's that's the
你好，仅此而已
hard part right and then we're just
正确的部分，然后我们就
gonna say give me either the first one
要说给我第一个
or an empty model very very simple
或非常简单的空模型
couldn't get simpler ok and so we're
无法简单确定，所以我们
using the map really just to make sure
使用地图真的只是为了确保
that we have any don't have any
我们有任何没有
duplicates that's the reason we use the
重复，这就是我们使用
map but then we throw away the keys
地图，但是我们扔掉钥匙
after we've done the deed ooping to get
在我们完成契约之后
the list or the collection of publishers
出版商名单或馆藏
the the set of publishers and then we
出版商的集合，然后我们
use that to figure out which one comes
用它来找出哪一个来
back first
先回
ok so fairly straightforward right not a
好的，所以很简单，不是
big deal not a lot of code I mean
很大，我的意思不是很多代码
there's a fair amount of color but I
有很多颜色，但是我
think variables you know constructor
认为您知道构造函数的变量
know their constructors are really not a
知道他们的建设者真的不是
lot of code I mean if you look at it
我要说的是很多代码
this is most of the requests that's a 62
这是大多数要求的62
to 77 so 15 and then eighty five to
到77所以15然后是85
ninety six so 11 right so not a lot of
96，所以11对，所以不是很多
code right let alone a put it all I
代码正确，更不用说我了
guess I didn't need this I wonder why I
猜猜我不需要这个，我想知道为什么我
would've thought I was gonna do with
会以为我会与
that I wonder if that's important I must
我想知道那是否很重要
have had some intent I mean we were we
有一些意图，我的意思是我们是我们
were writing this code together my
一起写这段代码
friends I don't remember why I wrote
我不记得为什么写信的朋友
that what do you feels like that could
你觉得那可能
be useful oh you know you know what we
有用哦，你知道你知道我们
could have done with that let's leave
本来可以做的让我们离开
that here let's make sure you don't have
在这里，请确保您没有
to do this but let's say that we want to
为此，但是我们要
make sure that there are instances of
确保存在以下情况
this service otherwise we're going to be
这项服务，否则我们将成为
will never get what we want right so
永远不会得到我们想要的东西，所以
there must be at least this dot of tips
至少必须有这个提示
instances of the service so techie okay
服务实例，所以技术人员还可以
so there's our we're just gonna make
所以有我们，我们要做
sure that we you know before we try and
在尝试之前，请确保我们知道
load balancing and all this stuff that
负载平衡以及所有这些东西
if you ask us to call three different
如果您要我们给三个不同的人打电话
instances that there are three different
有三个不同的实例
instances because that's what's gonna
实例，因为那将是
happen is in the next line or the next
发生在下一行或下一行
few lines we're gonna keep a count I'm
我们要数几行
gonna say okay
会说好的
while the map that we've built that
而我们建立的地图
accumulates all the different in-flight
累积所有不同的飞行中
requests is being built it's being built
正在建立请求，正在建立
against unique URLs if those unique URLs
针对唯一网址（如果这些唯一网址）
you know if the if the if we try and add
你知道如果如果我们尝试添加
something that is already it's that's
已经是的东西是
already been seen then then it's gonna
已经被看到，那么它将
well I mean let's get you know it'll try
好吧，我的意思是让我们知道您会尝试的
again mourn it and try and choose
再次哀悼并尝试选择
another one and we don't want that so so
另一个，我们不想要那样
that's not good you know the other thing
不好，你知道另一件事
it occurs to me is that in this case
我想到的是在这种情况下
we're actually using the load bouncer so
我们实际上是在使用负载弹跳器
I'm using the load balancer I'm saying
我正在使用负载均衡器
using the load balancer algorithm that
使用负载均衡器算法
we've got pick one from among the
我们从其中选择了一个
configured instances if you don't care
配置实例，如果您不在乎
about that load bouncer you could just
关于那个负载弹跳器，你可以
throw the first three service instances
抛出前三个服务实例
from this collection in the map right
来自地图中此收藏的权利
yeah you know as long as this list is
是的，只要这个清单是
greater than or equal to the attempts
大于或等于尝试
count you could just throw the instances
算你可以丢实例
that are in there that are you know
在那里你知道
before or at the budget that we've got
之前或达到我们的预算
the quota that we want you could throw
我们希望您可以投入的配额
those in the map and just you know
那些在地图上的，只是你知道
ignoring load bouncing just pick any of
忽略负载弹跳只是选择任何
them right but that wouldn't you
他们是正确的，但那不是你
wouldn't be able to take advantage of
将无法利用
the load balancer algorithm that's right
正确的负载平衡器算法
you may not care and it would have the
您可能不在乎，它会
benefit of being one call if you you
成为一个电话的好处
know it takes one call to make to get
知道需要一个电话才能获得
all three of these whereas conceivably
所有这三个，而可以想象
this load balancer client might have
此负载均衡器客户端可能有
calls to other things that have metadata
调用其他具有元数据的事物
that you want to you want to interrogate
你想问的
okay so that's a discussion maybe you
好，那是个讨论，也许你
performance analyze back I need that to
性能分析回来，我需要
you as an exercise okay so we need to do
你做运动好吧，所以我们需要做
our final thing here which is teach our
我们在这里的最后一件事是教我们
client
客户
about it EFS okay filter BFF good all
关于它EFS好的过滤器BFF都不错
right let's see what happens we have a
好的，让我们看看会发生什么
do have an endpoint that we can use to
确实有一个我们可以用来终结的端点
test this we do hedge we've got the
测试这个我们做对冲，我们已经
client we're making a call to sports at
客户我们正在致电体育
service okay we should actually start up
服务还可以，我们实际上应该启动
that service actually now so where's our
该服务实际上现在在哪里，我们的在哪里
service over here go
服务到这里去
one two
一二
oh-oh-oh I was a ambiguous I you know I
哦，哦，哦，我是一个模棱两可的人，你知道我
have two constructors spring doesn't
有两个构造函数spring没有
know which one to go with here's where I
知道跟哪一个一起去
use the app on a wire to the annotation
在注释上使用该应用程序
it's a it removes the ambiguity don't I
它消除了歧义，不是吗
just restarted the wrong one that was
刚刚重新启动了错误的
the you week uh service and then we
您一周的服务，然后我们
started okay so that's the client here
开始很好，所以这是这里的客户
we go services spitting up and down
我们去服务随地吐痰
here's our service restart I'm not sure
这是我们的服务重启，我不确定
which ones where we started which one
我们从哪开始的
worked okay that's one it seemed okay
工作正常，这似乎还可以
okay there's three of them
好吧，他们三个
all righty so it's gonna try all three
好吧，所以要尝试所有三个
in this case obviously if we did four it
在这种情况下，如果我们做了四个
would hopefully just try three not all
希望会尝试三个而不是全部
four but it's nice to know that it has
四个，但很高兴知道它有
the ability to to try it if it needs to
如果需要，可以尝试
and now we want to say curl HTTP
现在我们要说一下curl HTTP
localhost 8080 881 right we're not
localhost 8080 881对，我们不是
saying what I'm saying there's a service
说我在说有服务
client application which server port is
客户端应用程序哪个服务器端口是
it this is on port that's a certain
这在港口是肯定的
smother run the client here 80 81 right
窒息在这里运行客户端80 81对
good and the endpoint is called edge
好，端点称为边缘
okay what did we do wrong
好，我们做错了什么
failed to handle this launching it to
无法处理此启动它
that
那
well that's interesting do I have some
好吧，有趣的是我有一些吗
sort of weird DNS issue that's because
有点奇怪的DNS问题是因为
of my my hotel Wi-Fi huh looks like I do
我酒店的Wi-Fi，看起来像我一样
what happened there it couldn't resolve
那里发生的事情无法解决
so of course that didn't work okay so
所以当然不行，所以
let's see what you because saying Eureka
让我们看看你是因为说尤里卡
is saying it's got one client and three
说有一个客户和三个
service instances and the services and
服务实例和服务以及
the client for example is a unknown
例如客户端是未知的
mostaza okay well that's interesting
Mostaza好的，这很有趣
with the values negative so it's through
值为负，因此通过
an exception that's the issue
这是一个例外
aha so what happened here we got wrath -
啊哈，所以发生了什么事我们感到愤怒-
[Music]
[音乐]
is it really negative
真的是负面的吗
I guess that's I mean that seems I
我猜那是我的意思，看来我
didn't know this would do a negative
不知道这会带来负面影响
let's see next int second times there
让我们第二次看到下一个int
you go that looks like it's more easier
你去看起来更容易
so that's okay let's kill this and that
所以没关系，让我们杀死这个
one
一
to
至
three all right so the old ones are gone
三个好，所以旧的不见了
but there's still there's three brand
但是仍然有三个品牌
new ones here good so the service is
新的这里很好，所以服务是
responding that then that's not
回应，那不是
localhost but it's still an IP address
localhost ，但仍然是IP地址
that I have in my local machine then our
我在本地机器上拥有的
resolvable the client will I think see
我认为客户可以解决
these three let's hope
这三个让我们希望
close that close this so now there must
关闭，关闭，所以现在必须
be three instances in the service up and
是服务中的三个实例
running right now my client is the
现在运行我的客户是
heartbeat event for the client hasn't
客户端的心跳事件尚未发生
populated back it right so I suppose we
正确地填充回去，所以我想我们
could just force it and it usually takes
可以强迫它，通常需要
30 seconds for it to re-establish a
30秒后重新建立
connection on the service registry and
服务注册表上的连接，以及
then have a heartbeat event that
然后发生一个心跳事件
provides back to that to the client
提供给客户
where then refreshes its mochilas view
然后刷新摩奇拉斯视图
of the service but since we don't have
服务，但由于我们没有
that kind of time and I don't want to
这样的时间，我不想
bother with configuration right now or
立即打扰配置或
restarting starting from zero take two
从零开始重新开始
ok so hello after three seconds we're
好的，三秒钟后你好
3,000 milliseconds are three seconds
3,000毫秒是3秒
right let's see what our console shows
正确，让我们看看控制台显示的内容
here's the client here's the Eureka
这是客户这是尤里卡
here's a service this is after three
这是三点后的服务
milliseconds after four milliseconds
四毫秒后的毫秒
after four milliseconds okay let's try
四毫秒后，让我们尝试
it again
再来一次
so that one took three milliseconds this
这样一人花了三毫秒
one took two milliseconds the way no
一个人花了两毫秒
sorry your says again two to three so
对不起，您再说两三遍
one of those twos we'll have we'll have
我们将拥有的那两个之一
one right it'll have returned and it
一种权利，它将归还
says after two milliseconds so there you
说两毫秒后，所以你在那里
go the first one that returns is the one
去第一个返回的是那个
that we're getting back and and we
我们回来了，我们
aren't discarding the others but at
不抛弃其他人，而是
least if we have if we have a deadline
至少如果我们有最后期限
here if we absolutely must return on
如果我们绝对必须回到这里
time then this is a very useful
时间，这是一个非常有用的
technique obviously you can mix and
技术显然你可以混合和
match this a technique with other things
将此技术与其他事物相匹配
that are built into the reactive stack
内置到反应堆中
for example it is trivial to specify a
例如，指定一个
time-out on these requests because you
这些请求超时，因为您
know even if they don't return it even
知道即使他们不归还
if they're no longer in time to serve
如果他们不再有时间服务
the client requests you still don't want
客户要求您仍然不想要
them out there just you know off in the
他们在那里，只是你知道在
often the wilderness just waiting for
通常荒野只是在等待
something that's never gonna happen you
永远不会发生的事
should specify an aggressive client side
应该指定一个积极的客户端
timeout so as to free up the resources
超时以释放资源
we you know represented by that request
我们知道该请求代表
in the client so you can specify
在客户端中，因此您可以指定
timeouts you can also do retries right
超时，您也可以正确重试
the reactive if using the reactor
如果使用反应器则是反应性的
project which is the thing that
项目就是那个
underpins the reactive web client or the
支持反应式Web客户端或
reactive support and spring frame of
反应支架和Spring 框架
five there's support for doing retries
五支持重试
right I mean there's also two things
对，我的意思是，还有两件事
that you can do here but you know the
你可以在这里做，但你知道
the speed benefits we get her through
我们让她度过的速度收益
parallelism right those other things
并行对其他事情
ensure that your system cleans up after
确保您的系统在清理后
itself that you don't waste resources
本身就是您不浪费资源
which is valuable but in order to meet
这很有价值，但是为了满足
your deadlines we we fan out make as
您的截止日期，我们将散发出
many calls as we can in concurrence and
我们可以同时进行许多通话，
they return immediately and and the
他们立即返回，并且
benefit of that of course is that here
好处当然是在这里
in the client application in the client
在客户端中的客户端应用程序中
we're just making a call we've got a
我们只是打电话，我们有一个
publisher that has one value in it which
具有一种价值的发布者
is our string message we don't know that
是我们的字符串信息，我们不知道
this is in turn gonna result in three
这反过来会导致三个
other calls we don't care right our code
其他调用我们不在乎我们的代码
is much simpler logically because we
从逻辑上讲要简单得多，因为我们
just know that we get the first in their
只是知道我们在他们的第一
returns and then we can actually build
返回，然后我们可以实际构建
multiple calls using the same web client
使用同一Web客户端进行多个呼叫
all serves a service be in service see
所有服务都在服务中看
and I can use things like the flux zip
我可以使用助焊剂拉链
right I can say call a and B and the
对，我可以说叫a和B
result of that is if it's a flux it's a
其结果是，如果它是通量，那就是
publisher that has a tuple whose first
具有第一个元组的发布者
operand t1 is the type of the the
t1是操作数的类型
generic parameter of a the flux of a and
a和a的通量的通用参数
then type - t2 is the type of the
然后输入-t2是
genetic parameter of of the flux of B
B通量的遗传参数
right so you get you can do some very
对，这样您就可以做一些非常
interesting things where you call you
有趣的事情在哪里你打电话给你
know two different services and then
知道两种不同的服务，然后
compose the results in in a stream you
将结果组合成一个流
know you pull one from the left side
知道你从左侧拉一个
pulling from the right side pulling for
从右侧拉
the left side etc like a zipper that's
左侧等像是一个拉链
why it's called zip you can do all sorts
为什么叫zip，您可以做各种各样的事情
of interesting things like that and this
像这样的有趣的事情
is concurrent and you know it works the
是并发的，你知道它的工作原理
way you expected to it's just you can
您期望的方式就是您可以
call three services - obviously I'm just
打电话给三个服务-显然我只是
talking about some very simple cases
谈论一些非常简单的案例
here but that code each one of those
在这里，但代码每个
could in turn results in three calls now
现在可能会导致三个通话
do you have to worry about the
您是否需要担心
scheduling no as long as you're not
只要你不在就安排
blocking you know where then the
阻止你知道然后
scheduler on the default configuration
默认配置上的调度程序
should just be fine you can of course
应该可以，当然可以
you can customize the scheduler object
您可以自定义调度程序对象
that's used in reactor to change that
在反应堆中用来改变
behavior I want to think again I'm gonna
我想再想一想的行为
think John Schneider for reminding me of
认为约翰·施耐德（John Schneider）使我想起
this pattern John Schneider of course is
这种模式John Schneider当然是
on the lead of micrometer he's a real
在千分尺的引导下，他是一个真正的
smart guy you look at the code for a
聪明的家伙，你看代码
micrometer and
千分尺和
you can see this is we are very lucky to
你可以看到这是我们很幸运的
have people I came on the spring cloud
有人，我来了 Spring 的云
team helping build the most robust
团队帮助建立最强大的
framework for micro services all right
微服务框架可以
thank you my friends and with that we'll
谢谢你我的朋友们，有了这些，我们将
see you next time
下次见
you
您